mybillie.com 2019-11-30

# Billie | Privacy Policy

Billie Inc. (“Billie”, “we” or “us”), the operator of the www.mybillie.com site (the “Site”), is committed to preserving the privacy of those who visit and interact with the Site. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) outlines how we gather and utilize various sources of information obtained during your visit to and use of the Site. This Privacy Policy communicates how, when, and why we gather information about our customers and what we do with it. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites to which we link.

 **YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR ASSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE ACCOMPANYING TERMS OF USE (COLLECTIVELY, THE “AGREEMENT”). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO USE THIS SITE.**

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.

## Information Collected

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you place an order through mybillie.com for products, services, or a Subscription, we will ask you for your name, e-mail address, shipping address, telephone number and credit card information, and certain other personally identifiable information about yourself ("Personal Information"). We do not collect any Personal Information from you when you visit the Site unless you provide us with the Personal Information voluntarily.

### NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, duration and frequency of visits, and other data. We may collect this information from your activity on the Site, including information about time spent on particular pages, sections of the Site you visit, and other usage data, or from cookies (as described in more detail below). 

Information obtained in connection with the Site may be intermingled with and used by us in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than the Site including both offline and online sources.

## How We Use Your Information

We will not share or disclose your information to anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

### ORDER PROCESSING

We use Personal Information to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status. Telephone numbers and e-mail addresses are used to contact you regarding your order. In addition, when you respond to a contest, survey, questionnaire, sweepstakes or other promotional feature, we may ask you for your name, address and email address or other Personal Information. We do not collect any Personal Information about you unless it is voluntarily provided by you. 

All Transactions are processed by our third-party payment vendors. We do not collect, store, or maintain any billing information. Instead, it is collected and processed through these third-party vendors pursuant to the terms and conditions of their privacy policies and terms of use.

### ENHANCED AND PERSONALIZED SHOPPING EXPERIENCE

We also use Personal Information in order to give you a more enjoyable convenient shopping experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your Personal Information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site.

We may also track your past purchases to provide you with a personalized profile of your shopping history. In addition, we may notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information.

### AFFILIATES; CONSULTANTS; THIRD PARTIES

We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders. Further, in order to administer our contests, promotions, and sweepstakes, we may share your Personal Information and other information with our third-party promotional and marketing partners. These other companies will have access to your Personal Information and other information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law.

Unless you specifically consent to the disclosure of your Personal Information, aside from us, only our affiliates, technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who make our Site available or whereby our site is hosted, enhance its functionality, assist with the processing of your purchases, or provide associated services and/or who deal with you in delivering content, samples, products, gifts and prizes, have access to your Personal Information.

### LAW ENFORCEMENT AND INVESTIGATIONS

Please note that Billie reserves the right to and may disclose Personal Information or other information about you in response to (a) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (b) any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena; (c) if required by law; or (d) to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Site rules or policies, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper.

### CHANGE OF CONTROL

Please also note that we do reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information and other information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.

### AGGREGATE INFORMATION

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users, our Site, and our services, we might analyze non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Site and our products and services. This aggregate information ("Aggregate Information") does not identify any individual. We may share this Aggregate Information with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our products and services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### SWEEPSTAKES

If you submit your email address to be added to a mailing list or sweepstakes or other promotion, we will use the email address for the purpose of sending you announcements, special offers from Billie and its promotional partners along with Site updates. Each email we send will contain information on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

### REFERRALS

If you elect to use our referral services for informing a friend about our Site we will ask you for the friend's name and email address. Billie will automatically send the friend an initial email inviting them to visit or transact with the Site. Billie may also send additional emails reminding your friend that you referred them. Additionally, you may send additional "reminders" to your friend to remind them to sign up. Billie and/or our third party partners store this information for the sole purpose of sending these referral emails and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact Billie to request the removal of this information from our database and to stop receiving reminders.

## Use of Cookies

Our Site may pass a "cookie" (a string of information that is sent by a web site to be resident on your system's hard drive, and/or temporarily in your computer's memory blocks). The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a particular page. The Site may use cookies in on-line catalogs to keep track of your status and contents of your shopping cart. or to retain information gathered in cookies to allow you access to password-protected areas of the Site. You may set your browser to decline cookies. If you do so, however, you may not be able to fully experience some interactive features of the Site.

## Pixel Tags Or Beacons

In addition to cookies, we also collect Aggregate Information through the use of "tracking pixels," also known as "beacons." A tracking pixel is a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a web page and, in combination with a cookie, allows for the collection of information regarding the use of the web page that contains the tracking pixel. We use tracking pixels to tell when an advertisement has been clicked on or otherwise interacted with, and use that information to judge which advertisements are more appealing to users. In some cases, we use third party service providers to help us collect and analyze this information. You can also generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the **NAI website** and **DAA website**.

## Analytics and Remarketing

We use one or more third–party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate your use of the Site, compile reports on activity (based on their collection of IP addresses, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, data and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Site you visit, number of links clicked while on the Site, search terms and other similar usage data), and analyze performance metrics. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By accessing and using the Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

For more information on these third parties, including how to opt out from certain data collection, please visit the sites below. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Site.

For Google Analytics, please visit: **<https://www.google.com/analytics>**.

We also use one or more third-party remarketing services (including Facebook and Google Adwords) to advertise on third-party websites to previous visitors to our Site. These third-party remarketing service providers use cookies to serve ads based on a past visit to the Site. Any data collected by such third party remarketing service providers will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the privacy policy of such third party remarketing services provider. For more information on such third party remarketing service providers, including how to opt out from certain data collection, please visit the following links: 

For Google Adwords, you can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/). For Facebook, please visit: **<http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>**

## How We Protect Your Information

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. However, Billie will not be liable for disclosures of your information, including Personal Information, due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. We have undertaken commercially reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access to data retained in our servers, however, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, Billie cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or any information provided online, and you do so at your own risk. Users must accept all risks associated with any data transmission, including the risk that their Personal Information may be intercepted in transit.

## Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences

If you are a Member, you may access and update your registration information and your preferences to receive email or other communications from us by sending an email to Hello@mybillie.com.

You may also update or change your Personal Information or Preferences by sending email to Hello@mybillie.com. We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to fifteen business days as we process your request.

While we make efforts to accommodate requests to restrict our use of your information, we reserve the right to delete all or any portion of customer information if we are not able to reasonably accommodate a requested restriction.

## Enforcement and Dispute Resolution

Billie uses a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this Privacy Policy and periodically verifies that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible. We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information provided and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal Information.

## Children's Privacy and Parental Controls

This Site is not intended for persons under the age of 13, and we have no intention of collecting or soliciting Personal Information from persons under the age of 13. If you are not 13 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors. If a child under age 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

## Links To Third Party Sites

Our Site may contain links to other web sites. Other web sites may also reference or link to our Site. These "other" domains (web sites) are not controlled by Billie. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site to read the privacy policies of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other web sites. Visiting these other web sites is at your own risk.

## United States of America

Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States, you may not access or use the Site.

## California Residents

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to obtain certain information about the types of information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship (and that are not otherwise exempt) have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, including the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. If you wish to submit a request pursuant to Section 1798.83, please contact Billie via email at [Hello@mybillie.com](mailto:Hello@mybillie.com). 

Billie does not monitor, recognize, or honor any opt-out or do not track mechanisms, including general web browser “Do Not Track” settings and/or signals. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted. Please check this page periodically for changes to this Privacy Policy. If we make any change to this Privacy Policy that we in our sole discretion deem material, we will notify you in a manner we deem appropriate.

If you have any questions about the mybillie.com Privacy Policy please contact us at:

Billie Inc. 303 Spring Street New York, NY 10013 (888) 820-7422

Effective Date: This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on May 25, 2018.
